

050 - 5345340



Avishagoliel@gmail.com



M Portfolio

About me

Learning and user experience designer, with experience in leading E2E projects. Responsible, creative, with high self-learning abilities. Working in a dynamic environment that requires teamwork and the ability to think outside the box would be ideal for me.

Education

2021 – Today Direct track to M.A. for outstanding students in Instructional Technologies, second year, GPA 94

HIT

- AR interface design
- Creating an artificial intelligence algorithm for matching work teams

2019 - 2022

B.A. in Instructional Technologies GPA 92

- Web design and development using HTML, CSS & JS
- Educational games development using Adobe An

HIT

- Designing objects, images and icons using Adobe Ps, Ai
- Training materials development using Articulate 360
- UX/UI design for mobile devices using Figma
- As part of my final project, I designed and developed a mobile task game generator intended for tour guides of heritage sites with low technological literacy

15 courses out of the degree's courses were design related (approximately 500 hours).

Work **Experience**

2021 - Today

Instructional design & development specialist

National Fire & Rescue Academy

- Project management such as various digital courses for the HR department, logistics department and more, including tutorials, videos and quizzes
- E2E design of training materials, posters, marketing materials and presentations for conferences, the training department and the academy commander
- Design and development of content for courses, trainings and tutorials
- Creating a Decision-making simulator during emergency for firefighters and commanders
- Management of complex learning systems

Specializations and tools

- Figma / XD
- Notion
- G suite
- MS Office
- Adobe Ps, Ai, An, Pr
- Articulate Storyline
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Product design
- UX/UI
- Instructional design
- Web design
- Projects Management



050 - 5345340



✓ Avishagoliel@gmail.com



M Portfolio

About me

Learning and user experience designer, with experience in leading E2E projects. Responsible, creative, with high self-learning abilities. Working in a dynamic environment that requires teamwork and the ability to think outside the box would be ideal for me.

Education

2021 – Today Direct track to M.A. for outstanding students in Instructional Technologies, second year, GPA 94

HIT

- AR interface design
- Creating an artificial intelligence algorithm for matching work teams

B.A. in Instructional Technologies GPA 92 2019 – 2022

15 courses out of the degree's courses were design related (approximately 500 hours).

HIT

- Web design and development using HTML, CSS & JS
- Educational games development using Adobe An
- Designing objects, images and icons using Adobe Ps, Ai
- Training materials development using Articulate 360
- UX/UI design for mobile devices using Figma
- As part of my final project, I designed and developed a mobile task game generator intended for tour guides of heritage sites with low technological literacy

2009 - 2007

High school education

"Harel"

Full matriculation and 12 years of study

Work **Experience**

2021 - Today

Instructional design & development specialist

National Fire & Rescue Academy

- Project management such as various digital courses for the HR department, logistics department and more, including tutorials, videos and quizzes
- E2E design of training materials, posters, marketing materials and presentations for conferences, the training department and the academy commander
- Design and development of content for courses, trainings and tutorials
- Creating a Decision-making simulator during emergency for firefighters and commanders
- Management of complex learning systems

National Service

2011 - 2009

Association for the Advancement of Education and Welfare

Working with at-risk children at an impoverished neighborhood

Specializations and tools

- Figma / XD
- Notion
- G suite
- MS Office
- Adobe Ps, Ai, An, Pr
- Articulate Storyline
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Product design
- UX/UI
- Instructional design
- Web design
- Projects Management

Product Designer

My Portfolio

050 – 5345340

Avishagoliel@gmail.com

About me

Learning and user experience designer, with experience in leading E2E projects. Responsible, creative, with high self-learning abilities. Working in a dynamic environment that requires teamwork and the ability to think outside the box would be ideal for me.

Education

2021 – Today Direct track to M.A. for outstanding students in Instructional Technologies, second year, GPA 94

• AR interface design

Creating an artificial intelligence algorithm for matching work teams

2019 – 2022 B.A. in Instructional Technologies, HIT, GPA 92

• Web design and development using HTML, CSS & JS

• Educational games development using Adobe An

• Designing objects, images and icons using Adobe Ps, Ai

• Training materials development using Articulate 360

• UX/UI design for mobile devices using Figma

 As part of my final project, I designed and developed a mobile task game generator intended for tour guides of heritage sites with low technological literacy
15 courses out of the degree's courses were design

related (approximately 500 hours).

Work Experience

2021 - Today Instructional design & development specialist

National Fire & Rescue Academy

HIT

- Project management such as various digital courses for the HR department, logistics department and more, including tutorials, videos and quizzes
- E2E design of training materials, posters, marketing materials and presentations for conferences, the training department and the academy commander
- Design and development of content for courses, trainings and tutorials
- Creating a Decision-making simulator during emergency for firefighters and commanders
- Management of complex learning systems

Specializations and tools

- Figma / XD
- Notion
- G suite
- MS Office
- Adobe Ps, Ai, An, Pr
- Articulate Storyline
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Product design
- UX/UI
- Instructional design
- Web design
- Projects Management

Product Designer

My Portfolio

050 – 5345340

✓ <u>Avishagoliel@gmail.com</u>

Education

About me

Learning and user experience designer, with experience in leading E2E projects. Responsible, creative, with high self-learning abilities. Working in a dynamic environment that requires teamwork and the ability to think outside the box would be ideal for me.

2021 – Today Direct track to M.A. for outstanding students in Instructional Technologies, second year, GPA 94

• AR interface design

Creating an artificial intelligence algorithm for matching work teams

2019 – 2022 B.A. in Instructional Technologies, HIT, GPA 92

HIT

- Web design and development using HTML, CSS & JS
- Educational games development using Adobe An
- Designing objects, images and icons using Adobe Ps, Ai
- Training materials development using Articulate 360
- UX/UI design for mobile devices using Figma
- As part of my final project, I designed and developed a mobile task game generator intended for tour guides of heritage sites with low technological literacy

15 courses out of the degree's courses were design related (approximately 500 hours).

Work Experience

2021 - Today Instructional design & development specialist

National Fire & Rescue Academy

- Project management such as various digital courses for the HR department, logistics department and more, including tutorials, videos and guizzes
- E2E design of training materials, posters, marketing materials and presentations for conferences, the training department and the academy commander
- Design and development of content for courses, trainings and tutorials
- Creating a Decision-making simulator during emergency for firefighters and commanders
- Management of complex learning systems

Specializations and tools

- Figma / XD
- Notion
- G suite
- MS Office
- Adobe Ps, Ai, An, Pr
- Articulate Storyline
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Product design
- UX/UI
- Instructional design
- Web design
- Projects Management